cheatsguru.com 2019-02-16

# Privacy Policy @ CheatsGuru.Com

## _Effective as of October 2, 2018_

We at CheatsGuru.com (the "Site") respect the privacy concerns of the users of this Site and have created this privacy policy to explain:

(1) what information we gather from you when you visit our Site,

(2) how we may use such information,

(3) your choices concerning how we may use such information,

(4) the security measures we take to protect such information, and

(5) how you can contact us regarding privacy-related questions.

Some information is collected on this Site automatically through our technology; other information is collected only when you choose to give it to us.

## Notice to EU Residents

This Policy is intended to provide adequate and consistent safeguards for the handling of personal information in accordance with Directive 95/46/EC of the European Parliament and of the Council of 24 October 1995 on the protection of individuals with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data ("the Directive") and all the relevant transposing legislation of the Directive in the European Union/European Economic Area, the Swiss Federal Data Protection Act, as such laws may from time to time be amended and valid during the application of this Policy, the Privacy Shield, and any other privacy laws, regulations and principles concerning the collection, storage, use, transfer and other processing of personal data transferred from the European Economic Area or Switzerland to the United States including but not limited to the Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC ("the General Data Protection Regulation") as of its entry into force on 25 May 2018.

## Information We Gather Automatically

When you visit this Site, certain non-personally identifying information is recorded automatically by the standard operation of our Internet servers. Information such as the type of browser being used, its operating system, and your computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address (a number that your Internet service provider assigns to your computer whenever you surf the Internet) in order to facilitate our online operations and to assure an efficient online experience for you. We may use or share this information for security purposes, to generate group statistics about our user community, or as required by law.

Among the purposes for which we may use such generally non-personally identifying information is for identification purposes in the event of an emergency threatening life or property, or where proper legal process allows using such information. For instance, we may use your IP address or other automatically recorded information, in cooperation with your Internet provider, to attempt to identify you if it is necessary to contact you or to bring legal action against you because you are violating the Terms of Service for use of this Site, may be causing injury to or interference (intentionally or unintentionally) with our company's rights or property, or may be adversely affecting other users of this Site or anyone else who could be harmed by your activities.

The Site utilizes "cookies". A "cookie" is a small text file that an Internet site can place on your computer's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies make using this Site easier by, among other things, saving your preferences for you and to help identify you whenever you return to our Site. Most Internet browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. However, you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to alert you when a cookie is being sent (note: you may need to consult your browser's "Help" area for instructions on how to do that).

Some of our Site�s pages may also contain electronic images called "Clear GIFs", "Single-Pixel GIFs", or "Web Beacons". Clear GIFs primarily compile aggregated, anonymous statistics about our Site. For example, Clear GIFs allow us to count page views and to access cookies. In general, any electronic image viewed as part of a web page, including an ad banner, can act as a Clear GIF. Typically, though, Clear GIFs are very small (1-by-1 pixel size) files. They are often invisible on a web page, but their presence can be detected within many Internet browsers by setting your browser to view web page "sources". Clear GIFs are so small in order not to use valuable space on the computer screen that is better used to display helpful content. We may also include Clear GIFs in our email correspondence in order to determine information about the opening and reading of such emails. In addition, some advertising networks that serve ads on our Site may occasionally use Clear GIFs within banner advertisements.

Clear GIFs set by us on the Site and in our email correspondence generally are not used to collect, gather, monitor, or share Personal Information about our users, though they can be used in conjunction with cookies to record particular actions. We use Clear GIFs primarily to compile aggregated, anonymous statistics about the Site and our email correspondence.

## Personal Information You Provide to Us

We may request personally identifying information from you in a variety of contexts. For example, you may provide such data to us if you: (1) complete an online registration form (e.g., registering for an account, various sign-up forms for receiving email newsletters, registering for special offers, entering a contest/sweepstakes or responding to a survey); (2) fill out an information request form; or (3) register to participate in message boards and chat rooms and other community features.

In such cases, the personally identifying information we request may include your name, gender, a photo of yourself, email address, mailing address and zip code, and phone number (collectively, "Personal Information"). In addition, we may collect other non-personally identifying information such as your country of residence, language preference, hobbies, and other information regarding your interaction with our Site such as your viewing habits and cheats submissions, preferences ,and other customized activities in which you participate. Of course, you never have to answer any of the questions we ask you (nor choose to view or upload any content or otherwise interact with our Site), but refusal to do so may limit the services we can provide to you.

When you provide Personal Information to us, we may use that data to create a **"My Profile"** page for you, which will be held in a database using reasonable security measures to protect the data from unauthorized access. Others outside CheatsGuru.com will not be allowed to see the data on your **My Profile Page** except with your consent (see "How to Contact Us" below). If you register to set up an account, you will be able to access your **My Profile** page at any time in order to update your individual Personal Information listed therein (see below under "How Can You Correct, Review, or Request Deletion of Your Personal Information?" for more details).

## How Can Your Personal Information Be Used?

Within CheatsGuru.com

We may use the Personal Information you provide us and other non-personally identifying information we collect to update you about our products or services or to contact you about exciting offers of new products or services that we believe may be of interest to you. You always have the option to receive fewer or no communications in the future from us by opting-out. You may opt out by following the instructions included in the specific communication you no longer wish to receive or by sending an email to [privacy@cheatsguru.com](mailto:privacy@cheatsguru.com) and explaining how you would like to modify your preferences (see below under "How Can You Correct, Review, or Request Deletion of Your Personal Information?" for more details).

With Other CheatsGuru.com-Related Companies

When you give Personal Information to CheatsGuru.com, where lawfully permissible, we may share that data (together with non-personally identifying information you may provide) with other CheatsGuru.com-related companies. As a result of this sharing, you may receive communications from other CheatsGuru.com-related companies that include offers of products or services tailored to your interests. These communications might include, for example, emails or mailed literature about new products or services, promotions, discounts, sales, openings of new facilities or websites or other similar information. You have the option to receive fewer or no communications in the future from other CheatsGuru.com-related companies that we may provide your information to by following the instructions included in the specific communication you no longer wish to receive, or by sending an email to [privacy@cheatsguru.com](mailto:privacy@cheatsguru.com) and explaining how you would like to modify your preferences (see below under "How Can You Correct, Review, or Request Deletion of Your Personal Information?" for more details).

Finally, without any specific approval from you, we may develop general aggregate data (i.e., data that cannot be used to identify specific individuals) about our user community that is partly based on information about you and your transactions with CheatsGuru.com. For example, hypothetically, you might be one of 1,000,000 customers between the ages of 25 and 35. We may share such aggregate statistics with other CheatsGuru.com-related companies without your consent.

Contest Sponsors

When you give Personal Information to CheatsGuru.com in connection with a contest, we may share that data (together with non-personally identifying information you may provide) with the sponsor or sponsors of such contest. By entering a contest, you are allowing such sponsor or sponsors to use such Personal Information and to contact you in connection with the contest and in accordance with their own privacy policies.

Outside CheatsGuru.com

When you give Personal Information to CheatsGuru.com, we may ask you to allow us to share that data (together with non-personally identifying information you may provide) with our promotional partners and third-party advertisers. In such instances, our general practice is to ask you to "opt-in" to share such data and information on, for example, a specific promotion, registration page or sweepstakes. However, in some instances where lawfully permissible, we may ask you to "opt-out" from sharing such data and information with a given promotional partner or third-party advertiser in connection with a specific promotion, registration page, or sweepstakes. If you prefer, you may give us blanket permission to share your Personal Information with all of our promotional partners and third-party advertisers. Conversely, you may also choose not to allow us to share your Personal Information with any other companies outside CheatsGuru.com.

If you consent to share your Personal Information with our promotional partners and third-party advertisers, you are allowing such parties to use such Personal Information and to contact you in accordance with their own privacy policies. You have the option to change your mind and to stop us from further sharing your Personal Information with our promotional partners and third-party advertisers by contacting us and explaining how you would like to modify your preferences. If you wish to limit or discontinue receiving further communications from a promotional partner or third-party advertiser, please contact that company directly in the manner indicated in its own communications with you (see below under "How Can You Correct, Review, or Request Deletion of Your Personal Information?" for more details).

Without any specific approval from you, CheatsGuru.com may develop general aggregate data (i.e., data that cannot be used to identify specific individuals) about you that is partly based on information about you and your transactions us. We may share such aggregate statistics with promotional partners and third-party advertisers without your consent.

Finally, we may use your Personal Information in connection with third-party advertisers who serve ads to you while visiting our Site. These third-party advertisers may use your information (not including any personally identifying information you may provide) in order to generate advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like to know more about this practice and to obtain information about how third-party advertisers use your information to select advertisements please click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

Service Providers

We may employ third-party companies to provide customer support, perform website-related services (e.g., without limitation, maintenance services, database management, web analytics and improvement of the Site's features) or to assist us in analyzing how our Site is used. These third-parties may have access to your Personal Information to the extent required to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

For Legal Enforcement Purposes

We reserve the right to disclose your Personal Information as required by law or in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against you if you are violating the Terms of Service for this Site or may be causing injury to or interference (intentionally or unintentionally) with our company's rights or property, other users of this Site, or anyone else who could be harmed by your activities. In such circumstances, we will, where possible, require such third-parties to maintain the confidentiality of any Personal Information so disclosed.

As an Asset of CheatsGuru.com

The information that you provide and that we collect through your usage of the service is also an asset of CheatsGuru.com and will become part of our normal business records. If CheatsGuru.com or a substantial part of our business is sold or otherwise transferred to a third-party, your Personal Information may be transferred to that third-party. In such a situation, you will be provided with notice that a transfer of your information is imminent, and you will be given an opportunity to opt your information out of the transfer.

## How Long We Keep Your Information

How long we retain your information depends on why we collected it and how we use it. We will not retain your Personal Information for longer than is necessary for our business purposes or for legal requirements.

## How Can You Correct, Review, or Request Deletion of Your Personal Information?

You can access, review, update and correct Personal Information you have provided us by clicking on the **"My Profile"** tab at the top of this page. If you prefer, you can also contact us by sending an email to [privacy@cheatsguru.com](mailto:privacy@cheatsguru.com) and explaining how you would like to update your information. If any information is inaccurate or incomplete, you may request that the data be amended. It is your responsibility to provide us with accurate Personal Information and to inform us of any changes. (e.g. new home address or change of name).

You also have the right to request the deletion of your personal data at any time by contacting us at [privacy@cheatsguru.com](mailto:privacy@cheatsguru.com). If you demonstrate that the purpose for which the data is being processed is no longer legal or appropriate, the data will be deleted, unless the applicable law requires otherwise. 

## Safeguarding Your Personal Information

CheatsGuru.com cares about the security of your Personal Information. We follow generally accepted industry security standards to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security and correctly use such Personal Information.

Despite many advances in information security technology and procedures, however, no commercially deployed method of information transfer over the Internet or electronic data storage is known to be 100% secure. As a result, while we do strive to use modern and commercially reasonable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee the absolute security of that information during its transmission or its storage in our systems.

## International Operations and Transfers Out of Switzerland and the EEA

CheatsGuru.com is a worldwide service. By using our Site, you authorize us to transfer and store your information outside your home country, including in the United States, for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. The privacy protections and the rights of authorities to access your information in these countries may not be the same as in your home country.

We take additional measures when information is transferred from the European Economic Area (EEA). This includes having standard clauses approved by the European Commission in our contracts with parties that receive information outside the EEA. We also rely on European Commission adequacy decisions about certain countries, as applicable, for data transfers to countries outside the EEA.

## For Parents Concerning the Privacy of Information on Their Children

We are a general audience Site that does not knowingly collect data from children under 13 years of age. If, in the future, we decide to collect any age-specific data on our Site, we will, at a minimum, take reasonable steps to ensure that any users who may be under 13 years of age are directed to another CheatsGuru.com-related site which specifically complies with the requirements of the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act.

## Message Boards and Chat Rooms

If you participate on a message board or chat room on this Site, you are solely responsible for the content of messages you post. You should be aware that when you voluntarily disclose Personal Information (for example, your name, street address, email address, or telephone number) on message boards or chat rooms that information can be read, collected, and used by other users of these services and may result in unsolicited messages, both commercial and otherwise. You agree that by participating in such online public forums, you will not use such forums for any purpose that is unlawful or prohibited by the CheatsGuru.com Terms of Use or the community guidelines that may be in effect from time-to-time in connection with such service. We reserve the right to terminate your access to this Site or to take other protective steps if you violate those terms.

## Links to Other Sites

We may have links to third-party-operated sites that sell or license certain goods and/or services mentioned, provided, or promoted on CheatsGuru.com. Unless a site is within the CheatsGuru.com domain (as generally indicated by a web address beginning with www.CheatsGuru.com), it is not operated or controlled by CheatsGuru.com, and any transactions that you may enter into with such sites will be subject to the privacy and security practices of the merchant with which you are transacting. **CheatsGuru.com, our parent company, affiliates, subsidiaries, and the officers, directors, employees, consultants, and agents thereof are not responsible for the privacy and security practices of sites not in our immediate control**. You should not assume that their privacy policies or practices are the same as those followed by our company or by other CheatsGuru.com-related companies. Visitors to any such web sites should refer to their respective privacy policies and practices. 

## How to Contact Us

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please contact us at [privacy@cheatsguru.com](mailto:privacy@cheatsguru.com). When we receive such inquiries about our Privacy Policy, we will use the Personal Information (such as your email address) only to respond to your question or comment. However, if your question raises one or more issues that affect our promotional partners, we may also share your question with them in order to provide a response.

## Obligations to Data Protection Authorities

We will respond diligently and appropriately to requests from DPAs about this Policy or compliance with applicable data protection privacy laws and regulations. We will, upon request, provide DPAs with names and contact details of the individuals designated to handle this process. With regard to transfers of personal information, we will (i) cooperate with inquiries from the DPA responsible for the entity exporting the data and (ii) respect its decisions, consistent with applicable law and due process rights. With regard to transfers of data to third-parties, we will comply with DPAs� decisions relating to it and cooperate with all DPAs in accordance with applicable legislation.

## Changes in This Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to modify, alter or otherwise update this Privacy Policy at any time. When we make changes that we consider material in our privacy practices, we will notify you in this space. So, we encourage you to review this page from time-to-time. We may also attempt to notify you of any such material changes to our privacy practices via email or by placing a notice on our home page. Each version of this Privacy Policy will be identified at the top of this page by its effective date. Your continued use of the Site after the effective date of any modification to the Privacy Policy will be deemed to be your agreement to any changed terms.

## Acceptance of This Privacy Policy

By using this Site, you consent to the collection and use of your information by CheatsGuru.com in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
